oliveadverts.com 2017-06-06

# Growing income made easy!

Privacy Policy

1.1. This privacy policy regards how we store and deal with your user information. 

1.2. You can only use this site if you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

1.3. When registering at **OliveAdverts.com** , you will agree to have read, understood, and accepted the following terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to any of these terms, you must not register. 

1. Cookies

1.1. Your browser must accept cookies.

1.2. You allow us to use cookies to store any session, unique identifiers, preferences, or any other data that will help us among others to identify you as a visitor or logged in member, and provide you with the best browsing experience at **OliveAdverts**.

2. Security

2.1. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it, If you have any questions about security on **OliveAdverts.com** , you can contact us at [Support](https://www.oliveadverts.com/index.php?view=contact)

3. User Account

3.1. Your email addresses will not be shown, given or sold.

3.2. Your personal email address will only be used for **OliveAdverts.com** to communicate with you and to send you a new password in case you request it.

3.3. Your payment processor email addresses will only be used for us to send your requested payments and to confirm what you purchase.

3.4. Your user password will be stored in an irreversible format.

3.5. Your user password will never be shown, sold or given.

3.6. The activity of your account will be closely monitored and recorded for quality and security purposes in order to provide you with better support and to act as an extra assurance against any misusage. Your account’s activity / data will not be freely shared with third parties under any circumstances and it will not be used in any other way nor to any other end.

3.7. Conversations between you and our support are private. You are not allowed to publicly display them.

4. Username

4.1. Your username will be kept hidden by default from other users if you sign up without a referrer.

4.2. Your username will be shown by default to other users if you sign up under a referrer.

4.3. Regardless of the default setting, you will still be able to override the display status at any time.

4.4. Regardless of the setting you have, your username will always be displayed in the Forum.

5. Advertisement

5.1. **OliveAdverts** is not responsible for any of the contents in advertisements shown at **OliveAdverts**. This applies to all advertisement information we may display.

5.2. It's your responsibility when you click an advertisement link, click a link inside the advertisement page or browse its contents.

5.3. All advertisements are the responsibility of its advertiser and you must comply to their own Terms of Service and Privacy Policies.

6. External Services

6.1. Transactions regarding all other payment processors are subject to their respective Privacy Policy.
